questions = [
    {
        group:"Books of the Bible",
        title:"On Sonnets",
        question:"What is the topic of the Song of Solomon(Song of Songs)?",
        answers:["Solomon's wisdom","Friends; family","The Isrealites","Marital Love"],
        correct:"Marital Love",
        value:30,
    },
    {
        group:"Books of the Bible",
        title:"In the beginning",
        question:"Which book contains the story of Samson?",
        answers:["Book of Samson","1st Kings","Leviticus","Judges","Joshua"],
        correct:"Judges",
        value:40,
    },
    {
        group:"Books of the Bible",
        title:"This is the end, my only friend",
        question:"In which Book does Jesus describe the end of the world?",
        answers:["Romans","Daniel","Revelations","Matthew","Revelation"],
        correct:"Matthew",
        value:50,
    },
    {
        group:"Christianity 101",
        title:"Deus ex Deus",
        question:"Who is God's only Son?",
        answers:["King David","Dennis the Mennis","Michael the Bible Teacher","Christ","All people"],
        correct:"Christ",
        value:10,
    },
    {
        group:"Christianity 101",
        title:"Homme",
        question:"What is the natural state of Mankind?",
        answers:["Perfect Children of God","Sinful in need of Christ","Dead, in the grave","All of the above"],
        correct:"Sinful in need of Christ",
        value:20,
    },
    {
        group:"Christianity 101",
        title:"Remissionem",
        question:"How does mankind achieve forgivnesse of sins?",
        answers:["By doing Good Works","They cannot","The 12 Steps","From One Another","Through Christ's Death"],
        correct:"Through Christ's Death",
        value:30,
    },

    {
        group:"Christianity 101",
        title:"Gloria",
        question:"What is the significance of Christs ressurection?",
        answers:["So Christ can finish teaching his deciples","To forgive our sins","To prove that though Christ, we can transcend death","All of the above"],
        correct:"To prove that though Christ, we can transcend death",
        value:50,
    },
    {
        group:"Quixotic Quotes",
        title:"Proverbs 15",
        question:"A kind word turns aside _____, but a harsh word stirs up anger",
        answers:["Love","Jealousy","Hatred","Wrath","Foolishness"],
        correct:"Wrath",
        value:10,
    },
    {
        group:"Quixotic Quotes",
        title:"Matthew 5",
        question:"Who are the people spoken of in the beatitudes?",
        answers:["All human kind",
                 "The poor, forgotten, downtrodden people of the world",
                 "People in various stages of following Christ",
                 "Sinners in the hands of an angry God",
                 "Nobelievers in pain"],
        correct:"People in various stages of following Christ",
        value:50,
    },
    {
        group:"Quixotic Quotes",
        title:"Word",
        question:"What is the word refered to in John1:1?",
        answers:["People",
                 "The Bible",
                 "The universe",
                 "Christ"],
        correct:"Christ",
        value:30,
    },
    {
        group:"Ethics",
        title:"To Pray or Not to Pray",
        question:"Why does a Christian pray?",
        answers:["Prayer is a useless supersition", "Prayer allows a Christian to communicate with God", 
                 "Prayer is only for the benifit to those listening","Prayer gives Christians anything they want"],
        correct:"Prayer allows a Christian to communicate with God",
        value:20,
    },
    {
        group:"A Life Christian",
        title:"When to Pray",
        question:"When should a Christian pray?",
        answers:["Continously", "Never", 
                 "Only before dinner","At bedtime"],
        correct:"Continously",
        value:10,
    },
    {
        group:"A Life Christian",
        title:"Forgivness Please",
        question:"How many times should we forgive others for a sin against us?",
        answers:["Exactly 77 times", "Never, only God may forgive", 
                 "Always","7 times"],
        correct:"Always",
        value:20,
    },
    {
        group:"A Life Christian",
        title:"The Judge",
        question:"When should you judge sins of people?",
        answers:["Never, Judge not lest Ye be Judged", 
                 "All Sin should be Judged by Christians", 
                 "Only to inspire growth and repentance",
                 "ONly to force poeple to admit they are wrong"],
        correct:"Only to inspire growth and repentance",
        value:30,
    },
    {
        group:"A Life Christian",
        title:"You and your Friend Johannes, forever",
        question:"Your friend Johannes doesn't understand God and is asking odd questions abouy God How should you respond?",
        answers:["Punch Johannes in the face for insulting your Religon", "Stop talking to Johannes", 
                 "Invite Johannes to learn more","Defend your Religion agains Johannes"],
        correct:"Invite Johannes to learn more",
        value:40,
    },
    {
        group:"Books of the Bible",
        title:"Jesus",
        question:"What are the books of the Gospel?",
        answers:["John, Mark, Acts, Luke","Acts, Romans, John, Matthew","Matthew, Luke, Mark, 1 John, Acts","Matthew, Luke, Mark, John","Michael, Gilbert, Tiffany, Heidi"],
        correct:"Matthew, Luke, Mark, John",
        value:10,
    },
    {
        group:"Ethics",
        title:"You and your friend Johannes",
        question:"You and your friend Johannes are out on the town, when you saw Johannes stealing from a store If Johannes was truly your friend, what would you do?",
        answers:["Go along with his plan and steal with him","'Hammar of Justice' (Call the Police Immediately)","Turn a blind eye","Instruct Johannes to return the products, ask the store owner for forgiveness","Instruct Johannes to return the products, ask the store owner and God for forgivness"],
        correct:"Instruct Johannes to return the products, ask the store owner and God for forgivness",
        value:30,
    },
    {
        group:"Books of the Bible",
        title:"Book of Jesus",
        question:"In which book did Jesus get reserrected?",
        answers:["Mark","Matthew","Luke","John","All of the Above"],
        correct:"All of the Above",
        value:20,
    },
    {
        group:"Christianity 101",
        title:"Fear",
        question:"Which action best demonstrates 'Fear of the Lord'?",
        answers:["Giving thanks before a meal","Hiding under a rock","Listening to your Bible Study instructor, without question","Crying when you hear someone say 'God'","Skipping church"],
        correct:"Giving thanks before a meal",
        value:40,
    },
    {
        group:"A Life Christian",
        title:"Fruits",
        question:"Are we able to eat fruit offered for another god?",
        answers:["Yes, after giving thanks to God","No, it is unholy","With friends only","When it will not cause others to stumble"],
        correct:"When it will not cause others to stumble",
        value:50,
    },
    {
        group:"Ethics",
        title:"'Elementary, My Dear Watson'",
        question:"What is the main purpose of giving to others?",
        answers:["Sharing the love of Christ","Having too much to spend","Having a conscience","To bribe others to stay at a church","None of the Above"],
        correct:"Sharing the love of Christ",
        value:10,
    },
    {
        group:"Ethics",
        title:"Fortune",
        question:"Why does bad things happen to good people?",
        answers:["God isn't involved in bad things","Hardships cause growth","Bad things don't happen to truely Good people","God does so for fun"],
        correct:"Hardships cause growth",
        value:50,
    },
    {
        group:"Ethics",
        title:"The capable wife",
        question:"Which of the following traits is most important for a capable wife?",
        answers:["Does housework","Loves her husband","Fears the Lord","Works hard","Supports her family"],
        correct:"Fears the Lord",
        value:40,
    },
    {
        group:"Quixotic Quotes",
        title:"Chocolate covered",
        question:"What would proverbs say we should learn from ants?",
        answers:["Tiny is better","We need no king, whatsoever","To acheive any task, we should work together","Farming is the highest achievement of man","We should prepare for hard times when times are good"],
        correct:"We should prepare for hard times when times are good",
        value:40,
    },
    {
        group:"Quixotic Quotes",
        title:"Genesis 1",
        question:"Let the ___ produce living creatures according to their kinds",
        answers:["Sky","Church","Land","Air","People"],
        correct:"Land",
        value:30,
    }
];
